nutritioncuisine.com 2014-04-14

# Privacy Policy - Nutrition Cuisine

Thank you for visiting NutritionCuisine.com and for taking interest in our Privacy Policy. We have built this site with the objective of making it a valuable resource for you, and understand the importance of your privacy. We’re very aware of the need to respect, and protect the privacy of all our readers. We attempt to honor or exceed the legal requirements for medical/health information privacy for the state of New York, and the United States of America in general.

Please read this Policy carefully. If you have any questions about this Policy or our data collection, use or disclosure practices, please contact us.

This Privacy Policy applies to the Fast Forward Interactive Web Sites (“Sites”) owned and operated by Fast Forward Interactive, including the NutritionCuisine.com site. Reference to “Fast Forward Interactive” means Fast Forward Interactive, Inc., including any company that Fast Forward Interactive, Inc. controls (for example, a subsidiary that Fast Forward Interactive, Inc. owns). Fast Forward Interactive Web Sites include any site that Fast Forward Interactive owns or controls (for example, Men’s Health Base). Fast Forward Interactive may share information among its subsidiaries or sites that it owns or controls, but it is always protected under the terms of this Privacy Policy.

What information do we collect?

Since Fast Forward Interactive’s purpose is to provide you with detailed health care information, we may request correspondingly detailed personal health information. Certain information that we request is necessary for us to provide one or more Fast Forward Interactive services to you. Other information is optional. However, if you elect not to provide this optional information, this choice may limit the value of the Fast Forward Interactive experience for you. For example, if we do not have your children’s ages, we will not be able to provide information about their developmental stages or suggestions for age appropriate games and activities. As you can see, the more information we have about you, the more valuable the Fast Forward Interactive experience can be for you.

Fast Forward Interactive may collect or track the e-mail addresses of visitors that communicate with the Sites via e-mail and information knowingly provided by the visitor in online registration forms, information requests, the “Contact Us” section of the Sites, and other online resources. We collect personal information through our registration form and also from registration information you provide to our marketing partners (for users that join the Sites though one of our partners). Information collected at registration includes, but is not limited to, name, address, email address, gender and birth date. You may choose to provide additional information, including (but not limited to) such health and lifestyle information about you and your family as marital status and household information (spouse, children, pets, etc.); ethnicity; education; income; occupation; purchasing habits; reading habits; insurance; height; weight; physical and mental health conditions and diseases; symptoms; treatments; medications; medical devices; vitamins; health habits; and participation in research surveys and clinical trials. Generally, in addition to the other uses and features described in this Privacy Policy, we use this information to improve the Sites user experience by tailoring the content displayed in your version of the Site to the information that we describe in this paragraph.

In addition, we might receive information about you from outside sources and add it to the Sites membership information. We do this to improve personalization of our services (for example, providing better newsletter content, advertising or special offers that we think will interest you). We also may compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending identical messages to our members.

Even if you do not register with the Sites, we collect or track non-personal information including (1) the home server domain names, e-mail addresses, type of client computer, files downloaded, search engine used, operating system, and type of Web browser of visitors to the Site, and (2) aggregate and user-specific information regarding which pages Site visitors access, using tracking technologies, such as action tags or cookies.

Cookies

We and our advertisers collect anonymous information about your use of our site through cookies. Sites may place “cookies” on your hard drive. The cookie does not tell us who you are. Only you can tell us that. Internet cookies are small text files that save data about individual visitors, save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit the Web Site, and help us to deliver personalized content and other services. Many Web browsers are automatically set to accept cookies. You may change your browser settings to either reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is about to be placed on your computer. Please note, however, that rejecting cookies while visiting the Web Site may result in certain parts of the Web Site not operating correctly or as efficiently as if they were allowed. For example, if you are a member of the Site, you may need to enter your username and password each time you visit the Site.

The information collected by cookies helps us generate customized content, and also allows us to statistically monitor how many people are using our site and for what purpose. For contests or sweepstakes, we may use cookies in order to track your progress and the number of entries in some promotions. For polls, we may use cookies to help ensure that an individual can’t vote more than once on a particular question or issue. We do not store any identifying information in any cookies on your computer.

Third-Party Advertising

Our Web advertising partners, such as DoubleClick, may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser in order to control the sequence of advertisements you see and to make sure you don’t see the same ad too many times. DoubleClick does not use information collected via these cookies in its advertising network. To turn off DoubleClick cookies, please visit the DoubleClick website. If you opt out of DoubleClick cookies, you will still see advertisements on our site. These ads will be targeted only on the basis of the non-personal information that is automatically transmitted on the Internet, such as information collected in our Web logs and the approximate geographic location of your computer.

We also have agreements with companies, sometimes called “Ad Networks,” that serve advertising on behalf of third parties. These Ad Networks may place or recognize a unique cookie, sometimes called a “third party cookie,” on your browser. Ad Networks use cookies to understand Web usage patterns of people who see advertisements, to control the sequence of advertisements you see, to provide you with the most relevant advertising, and to make sure you don’t see the same ad too many times. Ad Networks may connect information about pages you visited on our site with information about pages you visit on other sites and show you advertising based on this combined information. While we do not control Ad Networks or what they do with the information they collect, we have relationships only with organizations that have agreed to participate in the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) and abide by NAI principles, which prohibit members from connecting personally identifiable information to information they collect through cookies without your explicit consent.

If you wish to opt out of participating in advertising programs conducted by DoubleClick or Ad Networks, please go to the NAI Opt-Out site and follow the instructions on that site. After you opt out, you will still see advertising on our site, but this advertising will not be tailored to your Web preferences and usage patterns. Please see our Advertising policy for more information about our relationship with advertisers.

Your browser software can be set to reject all cookies or to accept cookies only from our site. Most browsers offer instructions on how to reset the browser to reject cookies in the “Help” section of the toolbar. If you reject our cookies, you may not be able to log in or use certain functions and conveniences of our site.

In some instances we may include certain links in our e-mails that will allow us to monitor whether you access specific content or advertisements contained in that e-mail. When you click on one of these links, we will record that click and certain activities on the Web page associated with that link. We may use this information for various purposes, such as to conduct internal research on our users’ demographics, interests, and behavior in and to our e-mail advertisements and content. We also use it to customize the content displayed on your version of the Site, tailoring it to your interests.

Search

When you search on our site, we store the search terms and the site(s) visited so that we can continuously improve the quality of our search results.

Giveaways and Contests

We may conduct giveaways, contests and other promotions on the Site in which we may ask you for additional information. We use and treat this information in accordance with the terms of this Policy. Participation in such giveaways and contests is not necessary to use the Sites, and you may choose whether you wish to participate in any particular give-away or contest.

We periodically prepare analyses and reports reflecting visitor and member use of the Site and the Site services for our internal use as well as for a limited number of our business partners. These reports include aggregate information about Site members, and in certain instances, visitors to the Site. The information in these reports will not identify you individually. Our business partners who have access to these reports will not be able to contact you from the information contained in the reports.

Referral Program

As part of our referral program, you can provide contact information (such as name and e-mail address) of your friends and family whom you think would like to receive the Site e-mails and use the Site services. The users referred to us receive sample Site e-mails, but do not become members until they confirm their interest in the service.

Market Research

You may choose to participate in market research activities through the Site, including health panels and surveys. When participating in such activities, we may ask you to submit personal information. We may combine the personal information you provide to us with research tools and information from other sources, including prescription information. We use this information to perform research, and to prepare reports and analyses for our clients. Our reports and analyses to clients are made only on an anonymous basis.

Notice Regarding Online Behavioral Advertising

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our Web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

The Sites reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, update, change, modify or revise this Privacy Policy or the Sites services simply by posting such change, update or modification on the Sites. Any such addition, update, change, modification or revision will be effective immediately upon posting on the Sites. Upon any change to this Privacy Policy or our services, we may also notify you via e-mail.

If you do not accept the terms of this Policy, we ask that you do not visit or register with the Sites.

Please Contact Us if you have any further questions.

_Effective: September 2008_
